{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Data and Digital Communications",
    "Term": "Prefinals",
    "Title": "Quiz Reviewer for Prefinals",
    "LastModified": "18 November 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "05 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "This device is capable of creating connections between two of more interlinked nodes.",
      "answer": "Switch",
      "choices": [
        "Switch",
        "Modem",
        "Router",
        "Hub"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which if the following statement is TRUE  about the space-division switch?",
      "answer": "The paths in the circuit are separated from one another spatially",
      "choices": [
        "The paths in the circuit are separated from one another spatially",
        "It uses time-division multiplexing (TDM) inside a switch",
        "It is a source or a destination needs to have a global address",
        "It is actually used for data transfer"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which if the following statments best describes the User Datagram protocol?",
      "answer": "It is a non-frills transport protocol that does not establish connection and does not attempt to keep data packets in sequence",
      "choices": [
        "It is a non-frills transport protocol that does not establish connection and does not attempt to keep data packets in sequence",
        "It performs error reporting for the Internet Protocol and is commonly used by routers",
        "It is another small but important protocol that is used to support TCP/IP networks",
        "It is the most popular protocol that handles dynamic assignment"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the most popular protocol that handles IP assignment.",
      "answer": "Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol",
      "choices": [
        "Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol",
        "Address Resolution Protocol",
        "Network Address Translation",
        "User Datagram Protocol"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which if the following statements is true about datagram networks",
      "answer": "Each packet is treated independently of all others",
      "choices": [
        "Each packet is treated independently of all others",
        "It is a cross between a circuit-switched network and a datagram network",
        "It is normally implemented in the data-link layer",
        "It is a non-frills transport protocol that does not establish connection and does not attempt to keep data packets in sequence"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In switching fabrics, which of the following statements is TRUE  about the crossbar switch.",
      "answer": "It is the simplest type of switching fabrics",
      "choices": [
        "It is the simplest type of switching fabrics",
        "It is a multistage switch with microswitches at each stage that route the packets based on the output port represented as a binary string",
        "Another hardware module called a trap is added between the Batcher switch and the banyan switch",
        "The problem with the banyan switch is the possibility of internal collision even when two packets are not heading for the same output port"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This protocol lets a router represent an entire local area network to the Internet as a single IP address.",
      "answer": "Network Address Translation",
      "choices": [
        "Network Address Translation",
        "Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol",
        "Tunneling Protocols and Virtual Private Networks",
        "Address Resolution Protocol"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is TRUE  about the time-division switch?",
      "answer": "It uses time-division multiplexing inside a switch",
      "choices": [
        "It uses time-division multiplexing inside a switch",
        "The paths in the circuit are separated from one another spatially",
        "It combines the two results in switches that are optimized both physically (the number of crosspoints) and temporally (the amount of delay)",
        "It is normally implemented in the data-link layer"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which if the following statements best describe Virtual Private Network (VPN)?",
      "answer": "It is a data network connection that makes use of the public telecommunication infrastructure but maintain privacy using a tunneling protocol and security procedures",
      "choices": [
        "It is a data network connection that makes use of the public telecommunication infrastructure but maintain privacy using a tunneling protocol and security procedures",
        "It is the command set that allows an organization to create secure connections using public resources such as the Internet",
        "It uses time-division multiplexing inside a switch",
        "The paths in the circuit are separated from one another spatially"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "These are sets of established rules that dictate how to format, transmit, and receive data.",
      "answer": "Network Protocols",
      "choices": [
        "Network Protocols",
        "Internet Protocols",
        "Transmission Control Protocols",
        "User Datagram Protocols"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In datagram networks, it is where the destination addresses and the corresponding forwarding output ports are recorded.",
      "answer": "Routing Table",
      "choices": [
        "Routing Table",
        "Destination Address",
        "Efficiency",
        "Delay"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In virtual networks, this addressing type can be unique either in the inside network or outside network, internationally.",
      "answer": "Global Addressing",
      "choices": [
        "Global Addressing",
        "Virtual-Circuit Identifier",
        "Space-Division",
        "Time-Division"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the length of an IPv4 address.",
      "answer": "32 bits",
      "choices": [
        "32 bits",
        "16 bits",
        "64 bits",
        "128 bits"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In datagram networks, each packet may experience a wait at a switch before it is forwarded. This characteristics is known as:",
      "answer": "Delay",
      "choices": [
        "Delay",
        "Efficiency",
        "Destination Address",
        "Routing Table"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This protocol takes an IP Address in an IP datagram and translates it into the appropriate medium access control layer address for delivery on a local area network.",
      "answer": "Address Resolution Protocol",
      "choices": [
        "Address Resolution Protocol",
        "Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol",
        "Network Address Translation",
        "User Datagram Protocol"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In structure of packet switches, which of the following statements is true about routing processors.",
      "answer": "It perform the function of the network layer",
      "choices": [
        "It perform the function of the network layer",
        "The speed with which this is done affects the size of the input/output queue and the overall delay in packet delivery",
        "It uses time-division multiplexing inside a switch",
        "It is the command set that allows an organization to create secure connections using public resources such as the Internet"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In structures of a packet switch, this switching fabric has a multistage switch with microswitches at each stage that route the packets based on the output port represented as a binary string.",
      "answer": "Banyan",
      "choices": [
        "Banyan",
        "Crossbar",
        "Batcher-Banyan",
        "Bangtan"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In switching fabrics, which of the following statements is TRUE  about the Banyan switch?",
      "answer": "It is a multistage switch with microswitches at each stage that route the packets based on the output",
      "choices": [
        "It is a multistage switch with microswitches at each stage that route the packets based on the output",
        "It perform the function of the network layer",
        "The simplest type of switching fabric is the crossbar switch",
        "Another hardware module called a trap is added between the Batcher switch and the banyan switch"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This protocol's primary function is to turn an unreliable network into a reliable network that is free from lost and duplicates packets.",
      "answer": "Transmission Control Protocol",
      "choices": [
        "Transmission Control Protocol",
        "Internet Protocol",
        "Internet Control Message Protocol",
        "User Datagram Protocol"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This type of switching combines the two (2) results in switches that are optimized by the number of crosspoints and the amount of delay.",
      "answer": "Time and Space Division",
      "choices": [
        "Time and Space Division",
        "Space-Division",
        "Time-Division",
        "Global Addressing"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which if the following statements is NOT TRUE  about Internet Control Message Protocol?",
      "answer": "All ICMP messages contains only two fields",
      "choices": [
        "All ICMP messages contains only two fields",
        "It performs error reporting for the Internet Protocol and is commonly used by routers",
        "A type is simply a number from 0 to n that uniquely identifies the kind of ICMP message",
        "The first eight bytes of the IP datagram caused the ICMP message to be generated"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does TCP implement flow control?",
      "answer": "The TCP header includes a field called the Window value, that allows the receiver to tell the sender to slow down",
      "choices": [
        "The TCP header includes a field called the Window value, that allows the receiver to tell the sender to slow down",
        "The TCP software can dissolve a connection after the data has been sent and received",
        "The TCP header attaches a port address indicates a particular application on a machine",
        "CP can set a value in a field ( the Urgent Pointer)"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does TCP release a connection?",
      "answer": "The TCP software can dissolve a connection after the data has been sent and received",
      "choices": [
        "The TCP software can dissolve a connection after the data has been sent and received",
        "The TCP header includes a field called the Window value, that allows the receiver to tell the sender to slow down",
        "The TCP header attaches a port address indicates a particular application on a machine",
        "CP can set a value in a field ( the Urgent Pointer)"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In this type of switching, the paths in the circuit are separated from one another spatially.",
      "answer": "Space-Division",
      "choices": [
        "Space-Division",
        "Time-Division",
        "Time and Space Division",
        "Global Addressing"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It provides a connectionless data transfer service over heterogeneous networks by passing through and routing datagrams.",
      "answer": "Internet Protocol",
      "choices": [
        "Internet Protocol",
        "Transmission Control Protocol",
        "Internet Control Message Protocol",
        "User Datagram Protocol"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does TCP establish priority?",
      "answer": "CP can set a value in a field ( the Urgent Pointer)",
      "choices": [
        "CP can set a value in a field ( the Urgent Pointer)",
        "The TCP header includes a field called the Window value, that allows the receiver to tell the sender to slow down",
        "The TCP header attaches a port address indicates a particular application on a machine",
        "The TCP software can dissolve a connection after the data has been sent and received"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does TCP perform create a connection?",
      "answer": "The TCP header attaches a port address indicates a particular application on a machine",
      "choices": [
        "The TCP header attaches a port address indicates a particular application on a machine",
        "CP can set a value in a field ( the Urgent Pointer)",
        "The TCP software can dissolve a connection after the data has been sent and received",
        "The TCP header includes a field called the Window value, that allows the receiver to tell the sender to slow down"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a list of destination addresses in datagram networks.",
      "answer": "Routing Table",
      "choices": [
        "Routing Table",
        "Destination Address",
        "Efficiency",
        "Delay"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which if the following statements best describes Network Address Translation?",
      "answer": "It lets a router represent an entire local area",
      "choices": [
        "It lets a router represent an entire local area",
        "It is the most popular protocol that handles dynamic assignment",
        "It is another small but important protocol that is used to support TCP/IP networks",
        "It is a non-frills transport protocol that does not establish connection and does not attempt to keep data packets in sequence"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 Reviewer",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    }
  ]
}